(Sheldon:)Oh, come on, I'm practically
feeding you the answer.
(Sheldon:)I compromise.
(Raj:)Hey, uh, thanks for
keeping me company.
I'm happy to.
(Howard:)I think getting out of
the apartment will do you good.
(Howard:)So... where we headed?
(Raj:)If it's okay with you,
I'd like to go to temple.
(Howard:)Buddy, trust me, you don't want
to convert to Judaism.
(Howard:)I mean, I know I make it
look cool,
(Howard:)but... it's not all briskets
and dreidels.
(Raj:)I meant a Hindu temple.
(Howard:)Oh. Okay.
It's not like Indiana Jones
and the Temple of Doom, right?
(Howard:)Some bald guy with horns
isn't gonna rip my heart out.
(Raj:)Dude, that movie's
an imperialist fantasy
(Raj:)that makes the followers of a
beautiful and peaceful religion
(Raj:)look like a bunch
of bloodthirsty barbarians.
(Howard:)You love that movie.
(Raj:)Yeah, it's pretty great.
(Howard:)I'm surprised to see you
suddenly get religious.